SAJID QURESHI

Peshawar Pakistan • 03028001920 • sajidq046@gmail.com



Front End Developer / UI UX Designer

Summary

I am a dreamer and a fanatic of all digital things. I've been coding for the last 2.5 years and I love it. I' am graduated as a Software Engineer. I have developed a lot of websites and web applications using a combination of Front End technologies. During my old days, I have used HTML, CSS, JavaScript, Bootstrap ,tailwind ,saas , less , laravel, and Adobe Xd , Fogma tools & framework for building & Desiging web apps and websites .Looking for an entry into highly professional organization with Competitive environment, where I can use my knowledge and skills to achieve the organization goals and also get opportunity to learn new technologies.

Work experience

Jan 2021 - Present

Front End Developer / UI UX Designer

Last Wave Technologies

- Creates responsive, pixel-perfect UIs according to the Xd , figma design.
- Design Web Apps and Mobile Apps UI UX prototypes in XD, Figma.
- Create responsive custom dashboards, email templets and web pages.
- Developing Laravel frontend Pages & blade templating , routing .
- Wordrpress theme Customization , forms, payments integration & little tweaks in wp backend.
- Wordpress wocommerce setup.

Held additional roles with fellow devs.

jan 2019 - dec 2020

Front End Developer / Web Designer

Quinin Technoogies

- Fixing Bugs in Lead Project.
- Ensure the technical feasibility of UI/UX designs.
- Develop new user-facing features.
- Creating Websites that are user-friendly, effective and appealing.
- $\bullet \ \ \text{Wordpress UI/UX customization}. \\$
- Modify and customize WordPress templates to reflect the tone And style of the client/brand requirements

Jun 2018 - Nov 2019

Front End Developer

Tech Mentors Pakistan

- Use markup languages like HTML to create user-friendly web pages.
- Customize modern templates on client requirements
- Maintain and improve websites.
- Start working with the latest technology to develop responsive websites.
- Excellent knowledge of the latest front-End technologies, including HTML5, CSS3, Bootstrap.
- Web application development using HTML5 techniques.
- Implement bodybuilding interface based project

- Html
- Css
- Bootstsap 3, 4,5
- Tailwind Css
- Saas /Less
- Javascript
- Jquery
- Sound Knowlege of React JS
- Adobe Xd
- Figma
- UI UX Designing
- Laravel blade and routing system
- Wordpress
- Wp wocommerce
- Wp Theme Customization

Fimiliar With

- Git
- Git Hub
- Trello
- Jira

Education

2012 - 2016 BS Computer Science

Islamia College University Peshawar

Kp IT Board Peshawar Pakistan collaboration with UN And World Bank

2017 - 2017 Graphic Designing

Kp IT Board Peshawar Pakistan

Core Competencies

- Clean and well maintained code
- Code Testing
- Fixing Bugs

Created with **TVisualCV**